
Knox's Labelled Items (XML)
---------------------------

Knox's Labelled Items is a mod resource which aims to make adjusting equipment (all weapons and armour/clothing) variables much quicker and easier by including each item's in-game name in commented XML.

Previously, it was necessary to cross-reference 32-digit item IDs with their corresponding field in the text_ui_items.xml localization to identify the name of an item.
This resource is simply an alphabetically sorted & labelled collection of the following files located in Tables/Libs/Tables/item:

	- ammo.xml
	- armor.xml
	- equippable_item.xml
	- melee_weapon.xml
	- missile_weapon.xml
	- pickable_item.xml
	- weapon.xml
	- player_item.xml

Now, one can simply CTRL+F to search for an item's name to quickly find it and adjust values.

When editing values, please be aware of the following:

	- There are many duplicate items with the same name (presumably they use different models/textures) so you may need to modify the values of more than one line.
	- Duplicate items may not be sorted by descending item ID. When editing the values of a duplicate named item across files, it would be wise to also check that the item ID matches.
	- This directory does not include the sister .TBL files. To edit and use these .XML files in your own mod, please remember to include an empty version of each file's .TBL counterpart in your mod's directory.

Changlog:

﻿	Version 1.0 (released 02/04/2018):

		- ﻿All melee weapons labelled.
		- All missile weapons labelled.
		- All ammo labelled.
		- All clothing labelled.
		- All armour labelled.

	Version 1.1 (in progress):

		- All food labelled
		- All potions labelled
		- All ingredients labelled
		- All quest items labelled
		- All keys labelled
		- Include labels in the item.xml file